{
    "subject": "resource/The_Great_Mouse_Detective",
    "predicate": "ontology/basedOn",
    "object": "resource/Basil_of_Baker_Street",
    "human_readable": "The Great Mouse Detective was based on Basil of Baker Street.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9033573269844055,
            "question": "How is Basil of Baker Street portrayed in *The Great Mouse Detective*?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8643299341201782,
            "question": "Who is Basil of Baker Street based on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46624401211738586,
            "question": "What kind of character is Basil of Baker Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3933727443218231,
            "question": "What was the setting for *The Great Mouse Detective*?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3423309028148651,
            "question": "Besides being a movie, what else is Basil of Baker Street known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2584129571914673,
            "question": "What themes are explored in *The Great Mouse Detective*?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23316264152526855,
            "question": "Is there a real-life character that inspired *The Great Mouse Detective*?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21074426174163818,
            "question": "Can you name another movie that features a detective mouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20167239010334015,
            "question": "What was the inspiration for the movie *The Great Mouse Detective*?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17032448947429657,
            "question": "What famous literary detective influenced *The Great Mouse Detective*?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Great Mouse Detective was based on Basil of Baker Street.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7206_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the inspiration for the movie *The Great Mouse Detective*?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7206_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another movie that features a detective mouse?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7206_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a real-life character that inspired *The Great Mouse Detective*?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7206_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7206_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7206_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7206_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7206_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7206_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7206_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7206_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7206_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7206_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7206_52.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it is mentioned that Basil of Baker Street (the central protagonist of Disney's film, The Great Mouse Detective) is based on the classic Sherlock Holmes character."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that \"The Great Mouse Detective\" is based on or inspired by \"Basil of Baker Street,\" as evidenced from the details about Basil, the mouse detective, and his similarities to Sherlock Holmes."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}